Hey, I'm Andrew and I run the Offshore Audio
YouTube channel.
Working with Tayyab has been an absolute pleasure
.
Tayyab's edited videos for me for about eight
months at this point and has edited
some of my best performing videos with hundreds
of thousands of views across the channel.
More importantly, he frees up so much space
in my head so that I can focus on just making
better videos.
He's also been making thumbnails for the channel
.
Again, some of the best performing videos,
highest click through rates that we've got
on the channel have been made by Tayyab.
And again, one of the most important things
that Tayyab does is he always follows up, always
chases me for things that I say I'm going to
do and I never do.
He's always delivering professionally, always
delivering on time, and it's just an absolute
pleasure to work with.
So I could not recommend working with him,
whether it's for video editing or thumbnail
design.
Couldn't recommend it more.
Tayyab, thanks a lot.